# Islam Sabry Ibrahim

# Cost Accountant Accountant



- SolomSabry@Gmail.com
- **\** 01207780921
- 53 Mahmoud Younis St, Al-Osra Qua - Ismailia, Egypt.

#### **PROFILE**

I'm Islam Sabry, an accountant with a passion for helping companies achieve their growth potential. With my Bachelor degree and extensive experience in strategy and relationship building, I strive to provide innovative solutions that drive success

#### **LANGUAGES**

English

#### **AWARDS**

- The Ideal Employee Award in Rovy kids Company.
- A Certificate of thanks and appreciation for discipline and commitment presented by the Egyptian Army.

#### PROFESSIONAL EXPERIENCE

**HT Medical For Medical Supplies.** (10/2024 – Until Now)

• Worked as: ( HR Manager – Cost Accountant).

(9/2022 - 9/2024)

**4** 2M Electric Group for Medium and Low Voltage Products.

• Worked as: (Cost Controller - Cost Accountant).

**♣** Rovy Kids Company for Kids Wear. (12/2021

(12/2021 – 9/2022)

• Worked as: ( HR Manager – General Accountant ).

(3/2019 - 12/2021)

🖶 El-Motakhasses Company for Mobile Accessories and Services.

• Worked as: (Branches General Accountant).

• Worked as: ( Accountant - Center Manager ).

(3/2016 - 4/2017)

**♣** El-Motakhasses Company for Mobile Accessories and Services.

• Worked as: ( Branch Accountant - Branch Manager ).

**♣** Rovy Kids Company for Kids Wear. (3/2015 – 3/2016)

Worked as: (Customer Service - Sales Supervisor - Shop Manager
 Safe Keeper ).

#### **EDUCATION**

- High Institute Of Management and Computer, Port Said University, Egypt, May 2013.
  - o **Qualification**: Bachelor of Business Administration.
  - o **Concentration:** Information System Administration .
- o **Score:** 3451, 84.17 %, Very Good with Rank of Honor.
- ❖ Faculty Of Education, Suez Canal University, Egypt, 2017.
  - o **Qualification**: General Educational Diploma.
  - o Concentration: Computer.

# TRAINING AND CERTIFICATIONS

Data Analysis Certificate. (8/2024 - 9/2024)

> Worked at Al-Sheikh Zayed Preparatory Girls School. (2017)

Worked as A Computer Teacher.

Worked at Al-Salam Secondary Girls School.

( 2017 )

■ Worked as A Computer Teacher.

Information Systems and Administrative Affairs Certificate
 (In The Army) (2014)

> ICDL Certificate (2011).

> Human Resources Certificates:

(2011)

- The Power Of Self-Confidence With Dr. Ibrahim Elfiky.
- The Power Of Thinking And Change With Dr. Ahmed Koddous-
- The Power Of Persuasion With Dr. Tarek Darwish

#### SKILLS

### Computer Knowledge:

o Operating System Windows - Microsoft Office.

# ❖ Interpersonal Skills:

- o Teamwork and research.
- o Strong communication skills.
- Self and team management.
- Excellent analytical and problem solving skills.